A Guide to the Publicity Photographs of U. S. Senator Hugh Scott, 1958-1973
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- 1964 March 31 TV studio portrait of Scott (54c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 March 31 TV studio portrait of Scott (54d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 March 31 TV studio portrait of Scott (55a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 March 31 TV studio portrait of Scott (55b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 April 8 Informal (candid) shot with reporter (55c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 April 8 Informal (candid) shot with reporter (55d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 April 8 Informal (candid) shot with reporter (56a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 April 8 Informal (candid) shot with reporter (56b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 April 8 Informal (candid) shot with reporter (56c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 April 8 Informal (candid) shot with reporter (56d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 May 7 With Gene Cowan on Senate steps (57a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 May 7 With Gene Cowan on Senate steps (57b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 May 7 With CBS camera crew on Capital steps (57c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 May 7 With CBS camera crew on Capital steps (57d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 May 12 Senators Scott, Cooper, Jordan, and Clark at the Bobby Baker hearing (58a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 May 12 Senators Scott, Cooper, Jordan, and Clark at the Bobby Baker hearing (58b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 May 12 Senators Scott, Cooper, Jordan, and Clark at the Bobby Baker hearing (58c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 May 12 Senators Scott, Cooper, Jordan, and Clark at the Bobby Baker hearing (58d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 May 13 Press meets Senator Scott outside 301 O.S.O.B. for the Bobby Baker hearing (59a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 May 13 Press meets Senator Scott outside 301 O.S.O.B. for the Bobby Baker hearing (59b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 May 14 With Penn School and staff on Capital steps (59c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 May 14 With Penn School and staff on Capital steps (59d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 May 14 With Penn School and staff on Capital steps (60a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 June 2 Scott and Willy Brandt of Germany (60b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 June 2 Scott and Willy Brandt of Germany (60c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 June 11 Scott with Pope Paul VI and procession (60d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 June 11 Scott with Pope Paul VI and procession (61a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 June 11 Scott with Ben Gurion (61b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 June 11 Scott with Ben Gurion (61c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 June 18 Scott with Governor William Scranton in coal mine (61d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 June 18 Scott with Governor William Scranton in coal mine (62a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 June 18 Scott with Governor William Scranton in coal mine (62b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 June 18 Scott with Governor William Scranton in coal mine (62c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 June 18 Scott with Governor William Scranton in coal mine (62d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 June 18 Scott with Governor William Scranton in coal mine (63a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 June 19 Scott interviewed on Capital steps about civil rights vote (63b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 June 19 Scott interviewed on Capital steps about civil rights vote (63c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 July 7 News portrait for campaign (63d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 July 7 News portrait for campaign (64a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 July 7 News portrait for campaign autographs (64b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 July 7 News portrait for campaign autographs (64c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 August 12 Scott on Columbus Day hearings (declared a national holiday) (64d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 August 12 Scott on Columbus Day hearings (declared a national holiday) (65a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 August 12 Scott on Columbus Day hearings (declared a national holiday) (65b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 August 12 Scott on Columbus Day hearings (declared a national holiday) (65c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 August 21 Campaign photographs on the subway (65d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 August 21 Campaign photographs on the subway (66a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 August 21 Campaign photographs on the subway (66b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 August 21 Campaign photographs on the subway (66c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 August 21 Campaign photographs in Scott's office (66d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 August 21 Campaign photographs in Scott's office (67a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 August 21 Campaign photographs in Scott's office (67b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 August 21 Campaign photographs in Scott's office (67c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 August 21 Campaign photographs in Scott's office (67d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 August 21 Campaign photographs in Scott's office (68a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 August 21 Campaign photographs in Scott's office (68b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 August 21 Campaign photographs in Scott's office (68c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 August 21 Campaign photographs in Scott's office (68d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 August 21 Campaign photographs in Scott's office (69a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 August 21 Campaign photographs in Scott's office (69b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 August 21 Campaign photographs with the Capital Building in background (69c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 August 21 Campaign photographs with the Capital Building in background (69d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 August 21 Campaign photographs with the Capital Building in background (70a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 August 21 Campaign photographs with the Capital Building in background (70b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 August 21 Campaign photographs with the Capital Building in background (70c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 August 21 Campaign photographs with the Capital Building in background (70d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 August 21 Campaign photographs with the Capital Building in background (71a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 August 21 Campaign photographs with the Capital Building in background (71b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 August 21 Campaign photographs with the Capital Building in background (71c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 August 21 Campaign photographs with the Capital Building in background (71d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 August 21 Campaign photographs with the Capital Building in background (72a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 August 21 Campaign photographs with the Capital Building in background (72b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 August 21 Campaign photographs with the Capital Building in background (72c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 August 21 Campaign photographs with the Capital Building in background (72d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 August 21 Campaign photographs with the Capital Building in background (73a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 August 21 Campaign photographs with the Capital Building in background (73b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 August 21 Campaign photographs with the Capital Building in background (73c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 September 24 Scott at White House with President John F. Kennedy signing the Anti-Water Pollution Congressional Bill (copied from 1961 July 20) (73d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 September 24 Scott at White House with President Lyndon B. Johnson signing the Federal Airport Act (copied from 1964 March 11) (74a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1964 September 24 Scott at White House with President Lyndon B. Johnson signing the Civil Rights Act (copied from 1964 July 2) (74b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1965 January 4 Scott at the reception after taking oath for a new term in the Senate (74c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1965 January 4 Scott at the reception after taking oath for a new term in the Senate (74d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1965 January 4 Scott at the reception after taking oath for a new term in the Senate (75a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1965 January 4 Scott at the reception after taking oath for a new term in the Senate (75b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1965 January 4 Scott at the reception after taking oath for a new term in the Senate (75c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1965 January 4 Scott at the reception after taking oath for a new term in the Senate (75d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1965 January 4 Scott at the reception after taking oath for a new term in the Senate (76a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1965 January 4 Scott at the reception after taking oath for a new term in the Senate (76b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1965 January 4 Scott at the reception after taking oath for a new term in the Senate (76c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1965 January 4 Scott at the reception after taking oath for a new term in the Senate (76d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1965 January 4 Scott at the reception after taking oath for a new term in the Senate (77a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1965 January 4 Scott at the reception after taking oath for a new term in the Senate (77b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1965 January 4 Scott at the reception after taking oath for a new term in the Senate (77c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1965 January 4 Scott at the reception after taking oath for a new term in the Senate (77d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1965 January 4 Scott at the reception after taking oath for a new term in the Senate (78a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1965 January 4 Scott at the reception after taking oath for a new term in the Senate (78b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1965 January 4 Scott at the reception after taking oath for a new term in the Senate (78c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1965 January 4 Scott at the reception after taking oath for a new term in the Senate (78d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1965 January 4 Scott at the reception after taking oath for a new term in the Senate (79a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1965 January 4 Scott at the reception after taking oath for a new term in the Senate (79b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1965 January 4 Scott at the reception after taking oath for a new term in the Senate (79c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1965 January 4 Scott at the reception after taking oath for a new term in the Senate (79d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1965 January 4 Scott at the reception after taking oath for a new term in the Senate (80a) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1965 January 4 Scott at the reception after taking oath for a new term in the Senate (80b) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1965 January 4 Scott at the reception after taking oath for a new term in the Senate (80c) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1965 January 7 Senator Scott in Room 457 O.S.O.B. from a press conference (80d) (Box-folder 1:2)
- 1965 January 7 Senator Scott in Room 457 O.S.O.B. from a press conference (81a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1965 January 7 Senator Scott in Room 457 O.S.O.B. from a press conference (81b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1965 January 7 Senator Scott in Room 457 O.S.O.B. from a press conference (81c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1965 January 7 Senator Scott in Room 457 O.S.O.B. from a press conference (81d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1965 January 19 Scott with Governor Tom Dewey (copied) (82a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1965 January 19 Scott with Governor Tom Dewey (copied) (82b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1965 January 21 Senators Scott and Clark and Governor William Scranton at Appalachian "poverty" hearings, for the Senate Public Works Committee (82c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1965 January 21 Senators Scott and Clark and Governor William Scranton at Appalachian "poverty" hearings, for the Senate Public Works Committee (82d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1965 January 21 Senators Scott and Clark and Governor William Scranton at Appalachian "poverty" hearings, for the Senate Public Works Committee (83a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1965 January 21 Senators Scott and Clark and Governor William Scranton at Appalachian "poverty" hearings, for the Senate Public Works Committee (83b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1965 January 21 Senators Scott and Clark and Governor William Scranton at Appalachian "poverty" hearings, for the Senate Public Works Committee (83c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1965 January 21 Senators Scott and Clark and Governor William Scranton at Appalachian "poverty" hearings, for the Senate Public Works Committee (83d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1965 January 21 Senators Scott and Clark and Governor William Scranton at Appalachian "poverty" hearings, for the Senate Public Works Committee (84a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1965 January 21 Senators Scott and Clark and Governor William Scranton at Appalachian "poverty" hearings, for the Senate Public Works Committee (84b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1965 January 25 Scott on Capital steps, retouched photograph used in campaign (copied) (84c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1965 January 25 Scott on Capital steps, retouched photograph used in campaign (copied) (84d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1965 January 25 Scott on Capital steps, retouched photograph used in campaign (copied) (85a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1965 January 25 Scott on Capital steps, retouched photograph used in campaign (copied) (85b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1965 January 25 Scott on Capital steps, retouched photograph used in campaign (copied) (85c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1965 January 25 Scott on Capital steps, retouched photograph used in campaign (copied) (85d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1965 January 25 Scott on Capital steps, retouched photograph used in campaign (copied) (86a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1965 February 17 Scott with Author of The Agony of the G.O.P. in 1964, Robert D. Novak on a joint TV program (86b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1965 February 17 Scott with Author of The Agony of the G.O.P. in 1964, Robert D. Novak on a joint TV program (86c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1965 March 16 Scott with Clarence Mitchell of NAACP on a joint TV program (86d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1965 March 16 Scott with Clarence Mitchell of NAACP on a joint TV program (87a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1965 July 21 Senators Clark, William Proxmire, Dirksen, and Scott on a joint TV program (87b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1965 July 21 Senators Clark, William Proxmire, Dirksen, and Scott on a joint TV program (87c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1965 July 21 Senators Clark, William Proxmire, Dirksen, and Scott on a joint TV program (87d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1965 July 21 Senators Clark, William Proxmire, Dirksen, and Scott on a joint TV program (88a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1965 August 17 Scott with Dwight D. Eisenhower (88b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1966 January 12 Senators Clark and Scott on a joint TV program (88c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1966 February 8 Senators Clark, Jacob K. Javits, and Scott on a joint TV program (88d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1966 February 8 Senators Clark, Jacob K. Javits, and Scott on a joint TV program (89a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1966 April 5 Scott on committee hearing for transportation safety; Rambler (American Motors) heads testify (89b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1966 April 5 Scott on committee hearing for transportation safety; Rambler (American Motors) heads testify (89c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1966 April 5 Scott on committee hearing for transportation safety; Rambler (American Motors) heads testify (89d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1966 April 20 Trudy Haynes, KYW-TV Philadelphia; Senators Clark and Scott; and Gene Burns, WSBA York PA on a joint TV program (90a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1966 April 20 Trudy Haynes, KYW-TV Philadelphia; Senators Clark and Scott; and Gene Burns, WSBA York PA on a joint TV program (90b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1967 January 4 Scott on capital steps with a retouched necktie (90c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1967 January 4 Scott on capital steps with a retouched necktie (90d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1967 April 5 Senators Clark, Mark O. Hatfield, and Scott on a joint TV program (91a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1967 April 5 Senators Clark, Mark O. Hatfield, and Scott on a joint TV program (91b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1967 Scott presenting President Lyndon B. Johnson with his new book on Chinese Art, The Golden Age of Chinese Art (91c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1967 Scott presenting President Lyndon B. Johnson with his new book on Chinese Art, The Golden Age of Chinese Art (91d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1967 August 29 Portrait of Scott (92a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1967 August 29 Portrait of Scott (92b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1967 August 29 Portrait of Scott (92c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1967 August 29 Portrait of Scott (92d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1967 August 29 Portrait of Scott (92e) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1967 October 11 Scott watches World Series (Detroit Tigers vs. St. Louis Cardinals) and dictates to Margy (shows George Scott at bat) (93a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 January 16 Senators Philip Hart and Scott on a joint TV program (93b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 March 15 Scott receiving a pen from President Lyndon B. Johnson (93c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 March 15 Scott receiving a pen from President Lyndon B. Johnson (93d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 April 10 Senators Edward Brooke and Scott on a joint TV program (93e) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 April 11 Senators Edward Brooke and Scott and J. Irwin Miller of Indiana and others announcing "Rockefeller for President" committee (93f) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 April 11 Senators Edward Brooke and Scott and J. Irwin Miller of Indiana and others announcing "Rockefeller for President" committee (94a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 April 11 Senators Edward Brooke and Scott and J. Irwin Miller of Indiana and others announcing "Rockefeller for President" committee (94b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 April 11 Senators Edward Brooke and Scott and J. Irwin Miller of Indiana and others announcing "Rockefeller for President" committee (94c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 April 11 Senators Edward Brooke and Scott and J. Irwin Miller of Indiana and others announcing "Rockefeller for President" committee (94d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 April 11 Senators Edward Brooke and Scott and J. Irwin Miller of Indiana and others announcing "Rockefeller for President" committee (94e) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 June 5 Senators Javits and Scott on a joint TV program (95a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 June 5 Senators Javits and Scott on a joint TV program (95b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 June 6 Senator Scott and Representative McMathis confer outside Senate dining room (95c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 June 18 Governor Nelson and Margaretta 'Happy' Rockefeller at the Capital Hill Club (95d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 June 18 Governor Nelson and Margaretta 'Happy' Rockefeller at the Capital Hill Club (95e) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 June 18 Governor Nelson and Margaretta 'Happy' Rockefeller at the Capital Hill Club (95f) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 June 18 Governor Nelson and Margaretta 'Happy' Rockefeller at the Capital Hill Club (96a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 June 18 Governor Nelson and Margaretta 'Happy' Rockefeller at the Capital Hill Club (96b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 June 18 Governor Nelson and Margaretta 'Happy' Rockefeller at the Capital Hill Club (96c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 June 18 Governor Nelson and Margaretta 'Happy' Rockefeller at the Capital Hill Club (96d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 June 18 Governor Nelson and Margaretta 'Happy' Rockefeller at the Capital Hill Club (96e) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 June 18 Governor Nelson and Margaretta 'Happy' Rockefeller at the Capital Hill Club (96f) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 June 18 Governor Nelson and Margaretta 'Happy' Rockefeller at the Capital Hill Club (97a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 June 18 Governor Nelson and Margaretta 'Happy' Rockefeller at the Capital Hill Club (97b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 June 18 Governor Nelson and Margaretta 'Happy' Rockefeller at the Capital Hill Club (97c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 June 19 Solidarity Parade at Lincoln Memorial with Mrs. Martin Luther King Jr. (Coretta Scott King), Senators Scott, Charles H. Percy, Javits, Brooke, and Hart (97d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 June 19 Solidarity Parade at Lincoln Memorial with Mrs. Martin Luther King Jr. (Coretta Scott King), Senators Scott, Charles H. Percy, Javits, Brooke, and Hart (97e) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 June 19 Solidarity Parade at Lincoln Memorial with Mrs. Martin Luther King Jr. (Coretta Scott King), Senators Scott, Charles H. Percy, Javits, Brooke, and Hart (97f) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 June 19 Solidarity Parade at Lincoln Memorial with Mrs. Martin Luther King Jr. (Coretta Scott King), Senators Scott, Charles H. Percy, Javits, Brooke, and Hart (98a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 June 19 Solidarity Parade at Lincoln Memorial with Mrs. Martin Luther King Jr. (Coretta Scott King), Senators Scott, Charles H. Percy, Javits, Brooke, and Hart (98b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 June 19 Solidarity Parade at Lincoln Memorial with Mrs. Martin Luther King Jr. (Coretta Scott King), Senators Scott, Charles H. Percy, Javits, Brooke, and Hart (98c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 June 19 Solidarity Parade at Lincoln Memorial with Mrs. Martin Luther King Jr. (Coretta Scott King), Senators Scott, Charles H. Percy, Javits, Brooke, and Hart (98d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 June 19 Solidarity Parade at Lincoln Memorial with Mrs. Martin Luther King Jr. (Coretta Scott King), Senators Scott, Charles H. Percy, Javits, Brooke, and Hart (98e) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 July 5 Scott posing with Wendell Wilkie (98f) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 September 23 Scott and Representative Richard 'Dick' Schweiker at map (99a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 September 23 Scott and Representative Richard 'Dick' Schweiker at map (99b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 July 17 Solidarity Parade at Lincoln Memorial with Mrs. Martin Luther King Jr. (Coretta Scott King), Senators Scott, Charles H. Percy, Javits, Brooke, and Hart (copied) (99c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 November 22 Scott relaxing in chair while on telephone (99d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1968 November 22 Scott relaxing in chair while on telephone (99e) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 January 3 Senators Scott and Roman L. Hruska competing for position of Whip; Senators Gordon Allott and Robert P. Griffin compete for chairmanship of Republican Policy Committee (100a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 January 3 Senators Scott and Roman L. Hruska competing for position of Whip; Senators Gordon Allott and Robert P. Griffin compete for chairmanship of Republican Policy Committee (100b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 January 3 Senators Scott and Roman L. Hruska competing for position of Whip; Senators Gordon Allott and Robert P. Griffin compete for chairmanship of Republican Policy Committee (100c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 January 3 Senators Scott and Roman L. Hruska competing for position of Whip; Senators Gordon Allott and Robert P. Griffin compete for chairmanship of Republican Policy Committee (100d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 January 3 Senators Scott and Dirksen shake hands before Scott is elected Whip (100e) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 January 6 Senators Scott and Dirksen speaking privately; Senators Bob Dole and Scott (100f) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 January 6 Senators Scott and Edward Moore 'Ted' Kennedy conferring in Capital hall on way to House to count Inaugural ballots (both are newly elected Whips) (101a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 January 14 Senators Dick Schweiker and Scott on a joint TV program (101b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 January 14 Senators Dick Schweiker and Scott on a joint TV program (101c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 January 15 Scott and Secretary of Commerce Maurice Stans (101d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 January 15 Scott and Secretary of Commerce Maurice Stans (101e) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 January 15 Scott and Governor John A. Volpe, Secretary of Transportation (101f) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 January 15 Scott and Governor John A. Volpe, Secretary of Transportation (101g) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 January 15 Senators Scott and Schweiker and a Pennsylvanian congressman at press conference (102a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 March 12 Senator Scott, Bush, Brooke, and George Bloom (102b) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 10 Senator Scott, Secretary of Housing and Urban Development George W. Romney, and Jack Woolley (102c) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 10 Senator Scott, Secretary of Housing and Urban Development George W. Romney, and Jack Woolley (102d) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 10 Senator Scott, Secretary of Housing and Urban Development George W. Romney, and Jack Woolley (102e) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 11 Headshot with flag in background (102f) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 11 Scott with staffer, who was leaving for Army (103a) (Box-folder 1:3)
- 1969 September 24 "'For the Victor' - Scott embraces his wife today after he was elected leader of the Senate's Republican minority. Scott defeated Senator Howard J. Baker of Tennessee 24 to 19 in a closed door conference." (103b) (Box-folder 1:3)